For this eye makeup,
you can use this color as a base first,
and then switch to this color.
I have planned a few new tour routes.
Zhang Yang, take them out.
No.
Absolutely not.
No, no.
How about this?
- Tour guide Zhang Yang.
I will absolutely not agree to this plan.
Over the next few days,
we'll do a site visit of that route.
It would be best if some merchants are willing to cooperate.
Ms. Tang, we plan
to shoot some videos for promotion.
Zhang Yang and I will both be on camera.
We'll have to trouble you then
to help us with our styling.
No problem.
I said I won't agree to this plan.
If the route is well planned,
I can help experience it and give suggestions,
if you need it.
Of course we do.
Thank you, Yiyi.
This makeup looks really nice.
Are you guys even listening to me?
I said I won't agree to this plan.
- Lead tour guide, Zhang Yang.
Lead tour guide, Zhang Yang.
Right, his eye makeup.
We'll do it like this then.
Right.
Remember to apply a face mask tonight,
so your makeup goes on easily tomorrow.
I don't want it.
I'm giving it to you for free.
Who cares?
Cost items.
The cost items are...
Participation.
Relax, it will go smoothly.
How do you know it will go smoothly?
How do you know
I'm not relaxed?
Now I know.
Boring.
As for our project...
Leave the mask on for 15 minutes at most.
It's useless to leave it on longer.
You're really not cute.
Go to bed early.
I'll be counting on you tomorrow.
Fine, maybe a little bit.
Thanks for your hard work today.
Thank you.
Not bad.
I still have a bunch of things to finish.
I just remembered something.
It's extremely urgent.
I'll find you before we leave tomorrow.
Are you filming me?
No, I'm filming the table.
This table is such a table.
It'll be your turn soon.
Don't run away.
Whoever sneaks away will be broke for life.
I won't sneak away, I won't.
Li Xinyue, I'm going to the restroom.
I'll go get my lipstick.
Did they just chicken out?
Come here.
What's the rush?
Why do you have to say it in person?
You must not tell her
that I am that weird client.
Otherwise I'll be torn to pieces.
Then you can water our plants later,
take more photos of them,
and take some beautiful photos of my sister.
Okay.
Did you just secretly take a picture of my sister?
No way. Why would I take a picture of her?
Let me see.
It's pretty good.
About this place,
you absolutely cannot tell her.
Otherwise, she'll lose her temper again.
She won't. She won't.
It looks really good.
What part of it looks good?
It looks pretty good.
Where is Zhang Yang?
Dead.
Did he mess with you?
What happened? Why so angry?
I don't know.
Keep going.
Do we have to wander around the street dressed like this?
These clothes are so pretty.
Take a picture.
I feel like a moving tourist attraction.
Just imagine the picture.
Beautiful scenery in the background,
ethnic costumes and delicious food in the front.
How harmonious it is.
Besides,
don't you look pretty good?
Really?
Do I look good?
These clothes look so good.
Isn't it because I look good? Seriously.
At least we could eat it while it's hot in the store.
We came all this way,
and the deep-fried dough sticks aren't even crispy anymore.
How fast do we have to shoot to eat something hot?
The point is to show it off, you know?
Look, the environment here is so nice.
And the sunshine is so nice.
It'll look even better when we shoot later, right?
What do you think, Mr. Tang?
Not bad, Tang Yi.
When did you learn this?
Ms. Li just taught me last night.
Just call me Xinyue.
Exactly, just call her Xinyue.
Xinyue.
Call me Ms. Li.
Xinyue. Xinyue. Xinyue.
You still want me to call you Ms. Li?
You are putting on airs.
Who is putting on airs?
Who?
Alright, let's start.
Alright.
Hello, everyone.
This is Mianxianhu.
This
is one of our local specialty foods.
Usually,
we will add into it
small intestine,
oyster,
kelp,
and pork kidney.
Stop, stop, stop.
Are you reciting a menu here?
Eat.
And this Youtiao,
it's also very delicious
when added inside.
This soup base,
although it has soy sauce,
tastes very, very light.
Next,
I will taste it for everyone.
Then I must thank you.
This soup base
is rich and fragrant in every drop.
And I'm Zhang Yang, looking triumphant.
Watch me.
This braised food
is fragrant but not greasy.
This chili
is the icing on the cake.
This Youtiao
must be soaked in this hot soup.
Fragrant and crispy.
Much better than someone reading lines dryly.
Isn't it just four-character idioms?
This small intestine bursts with juice in one bite.
These oysters
are smooth, tender, and refreshing.
This kelp is very refreshing.
This braised food
has a mellow braised aroma.
This Mianxianhu
is fresh, mellow, and flavorful.
Take a smell,
take a bite,
it's a delicacy in the world.
Simply amazing.
Mr. Tang,
this take doesn't count.
Let's do it again.
I think this impromptu part is quite interesting.
And Xinyue, look at your current state,
it's much more natural than when we first started.
Is it?
Who made someone so nervous?
I had to use a little trick.
Continue.
Round two: A Bite of Nan'an.
Action.
Nan'an Runbing.
Full of filling,
the skin is tough but not hard.
Beef soup.
The soup is tender, smooth, and refreshing.
The beef is also fresh, fragrant, and refreshing.
This shredded ginger enhances the flavor,
simply perfect.
Minnan radish cake.
The skin is soft, glutinous, and chewy,
the filling is full of salty and fresh flavor.
That's right, it's tender on the outside and fresh on the inside,
with an endless aftertaste.
Move aside.
I won.
I didn't lose.
Exclusively developed by Chenggong Travel Agency,
the short-distance food tour
invites you to explore the old street for flavors.
You can choose a beautiful spot
and enjoy it leisurely.
The first order is free.
For the first twenty customers,
we will give away a food map.
In the map,
there are hidden ways to eat,
and some marked locations for you to explore.
We welcome you to bring your family,
lovers, and friends to consult.
Inviting you to join a lively
food appointment.
Nan'an delicacies, so good you'll want to take them home.
Come and explore the flavors of Nan'an with us,
and enjoy endless fun.
You said it well, but why do you keep squeezing me?
Why do you keep squeezing me?
I just finished speaking.
Are you going to shoot or not?
Just give up.
My face.
Mr. Tang, do we have enough footage?
Shut up.